Financial Secretary; Records ua305
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1928-1953; 1; 10 cubic ft. (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10)
  - Statistics on Finance and Administration, 1921-1934 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Summer Session, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Unit Cost-Presidents' Report, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Furnishing and Equipment Install, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Specifications on New Equipment, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Roof Repairs, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Special Repairs- Cornice Stone + Flashing, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Spec. Repairs. Water Main Service, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Repairs- Hot Water Heater, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Contracts, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - T.E.R. [?] repairs-etc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Alcohol Permits etc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol Permits etc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Alcohol Reports Applications etc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Auto Travel Mileage reports for O.P.A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Admissions and Club Dues Taxes, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Budget Director's Approvals, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Budget Matters, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Corp, Grants to Library for Books, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Centennial, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Coal Contracts, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cooper, Dr. Herman- Diplomas + Certificate, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Audit + Control, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dept.-Civil Service, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Exemption Certificates- Tax on Transportation for Persons, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gymnasium Floor Bloxonend Flooring Company, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Income Tax, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Loan Funds, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Leave of Absence + Rights and Privileges in Military Service, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - License for Explosives Chemical Supplies etc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Military Laws effecting employees abroad on Military Duty, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Aa-Al 1, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Am-Ar 2, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Athletic Council, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Finance and Appropriation, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ashes and Snow Removal, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Be-Bh 6, Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Ce-Cn 13, Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Cafeteria + Book Store, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Da-Dh 18, Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Department of Finance, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Finance Department, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Diploma File, Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Inventory, 1931-1932 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Supply Inventory, Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Albany Laboratories, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Leases-Rents, Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Loan Funds, Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Lounge, Undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Leases-Rents, Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Library Fines + Penalties, Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Loan Funds, Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Liabilities, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Payroll Information, Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Personal Service, Undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Processing Tax Certificates, Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Fees- College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Me-Mi(to Mn), Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Graduation Requirements, Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Li-Ll-Ly(to Lz), Undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - La(to Ld), Undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Rent Payment, Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Inventory, 1936 July 1 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Special Fund, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Special Fund Estimates, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Special Fund Estimates, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Special Fund Estimates, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Special Fund Estimates, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Special Fund Estimates, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Repairs + Alterations Special Funds. Chap 360, Undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Special Fund #10 Chapter 360 Part 1, Undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Electric Wiring Special-Pair-Funds E+W, Undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Steam + Water Lines Special Repair Fund S+W, Undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Roofs Chap 875 Special Repair Funds. R, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Appropriations, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Binding Books etc. For Library, Undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Dept. Audit and Control, Undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Dept. Civil Service, Undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Diplomas, Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Fee Accts- General Rules + Requl., Undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Extension Fee Budget, Undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Fees-Summer Session Budget, Undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Fees-Junior College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Federal Aid, Undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Income Tax, Undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Laws, Undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Leases+Rents, Undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Tuition M.H.S., Undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Report, Annual, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Report to President Unit Cost Receipts, Expenditure, Undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Payroll Information, Undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Annual Report, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1939-1940; 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1941-19422 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Budget Estimate, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Budget, National, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Payroll Information, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller's Rules+ Req's, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Civil Works Program, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Repairs to Bldgs. etc. floor campus, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Refunds, Requisitions + Lab fee, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Requistions-Approved+disapproved- Dep. Purchase, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Retirement-Employees, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ra-Rh, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Reports-Alcohol Permits, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Registration Rules + Regulations, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Reports of Moneys Rec'd To Comm. Taxation & Finance, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ri-Rof 58, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Sch-Sd 61, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Scholarship- Huntington Fund, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - She-Shz 63, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Si-Sn 64, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - So-Ss 65, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Special Services-Summer Budget etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Special Services-Regular Budget etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Special Services Extension Budget -Appointments etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Spelman Finances, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Stenographers-Clerks Appointments etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Sta-Sth 66, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - T.E.R. Maintenance Roads. Grounds. Walks etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - T.E.R. Student Aid Rules, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - T.E.R. Adult Ed., Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - U 71, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - V 72, Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - We-Wg 74, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Wh 75, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Wia-Wil 76, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Wim-Wn 77, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Wo-Wz 78, Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - X-Y, Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Purchase Order Forms, Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Regents Inquiry, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Printing Law Chap. VVO, Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Milne H.S. Addition, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Residence Hall Fund, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Financial Aid, Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Salary Lists, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - C.J. Dayo Treasurer, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Comptroller's Office, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Finance, Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Engineer & Superintendent of Buildings, Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Clock-Page Hall, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cafeteria and Bookstore, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Budget Requests, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Bro-Bt 10, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Binding-Books in Periodicals, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - S.S. Appropriations, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Appro. Requests from Depts., 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations Chap. IVO, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Special Fund Estimate, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Inventory, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Project Specifications, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Inventory, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Inventory, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - College and Milne Inventory, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Inventory, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Inventory, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Income Tax Figures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Class Gifts, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Gideon Hawley Shades Ventilators, Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Cash Books, 1844-1965; 2; 4.8 cubic ft.
  Contains a variety of cash books and ledgers: account ledgers, cash receipts for room and board, inventories, and library circulation statistics.
  - Normal School Ledger, 1844-1845 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - State Normal College - Journal, 1891 October-1917 July (Box 1, Item 6)
  - State Normal College - High School Department - Cashbook, 1892-1902 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Cash Book, 1895 November-1907 July (Box 2, Item 7)
  - State Normal College - High School Department - Cashbook, 1902-1912 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Sick Leave Book, 1905-1949 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - State Normal College - Registration Book, 1906-1911 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Cash Book, 1907 August-1917 January (Box 2, Item 4)
  - State Normal College - High School Department - Cashbook, 1912-1915 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1917 July-1919 September (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Cash Book, 1917 July-1920 March (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Cash Book, 1917 July-1921 September (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [1 of 3], 1918 April 1-1921 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [2 of 3], 1918 April 1-1921 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [3 of 3], 1918 April 1-1921 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - State College for Teachers - Journal, 1920-1921 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Cash Book, 1921 July-1924 December (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [1 of 3], 1921 July 1-1925 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [2 of 3], 1921 July 1-1925 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Smith Hughes Funds - Sundry Accounts [3 of 3], 1921 July 1-1925 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cash Book, 1924 December-1927 December (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Cash Book, 1927 December-1930 July (Box 3, Item 5)
  - College Inventory, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Inventory, 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Book Stock Record (Additions and Withdrawals), 1929-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Circulation Statistics [1 of 2], 1929 January-1945 March (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Circulation Statistics [2 of 2], 1945 April-1953 April (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Inventory, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General Cash Book, 1930-1933 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Special Service Fund Cash Book, 1932 July 1-1934 June 30 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Circulation Statistics, 1953 April-1960 March (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Receipts, 1953 June-1955-05 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Disbursements, 1953 June-1956 August (Box 6, Item 8)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Receipts, 1955 May-1956 December (Box 6, Item 4)
  - Room and Board Cash Receipts, 1957 January-1958 June (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Receipts, 1958 June-1959 August (Box 6, Item 6)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Receipts, 1959 August-1960 July (Box 6, Item 7)
  - Brubacher Hall Cash Receipts, 1960 July-1961 July (Box 6, Item 5)
  - Room and Board Cash Receipts, 1961 July-1962 May (Box 6, Item 3)